Search TFC:

Search

When searching for a date, please use m/d/yy. You can further refine your search by using quotation marks around your search term. (Examples: "3/11/18", "3/9/18 Senate Session", "state of the state" or "House Session")

1. [Home](https://thefloridachannel.org/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

The FLORIDA Channel will never disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to The FLORIDA Channel web site may voluntarily supply personally identifiable information in connection with registration for services which require subscription (such as schedule updates) and requests for videos.

The FLORIDA Channel may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above.

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of The FLORIDA Channel web site privacy policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of The FLORIDA Channel web site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please e-mail us at [florida@wfsu.org](mailto:florida@wfsu.org).

See What's On …

Click on Live Streams to watch today's LIVE events. Click on TV 24/7 to watch The Florida Channel's TV feed. Click off Live Streams or TV 24/7 to view a combined list of both.

Capitol Update

A full half-hour review of developments in state government, including Florida’s legislative, judicial and executive branches

Florida Crossroads

Florida Crossroads takes viewers on a journey of our state – exploring issues of state-wide interest in each half hour program.

Committed to bringing people closer to their government.

Suite 901, the Capitol Bldg | 402 South Monroe Street | Tallahassee, FL 32399

**Phone:** (850) 645-9030 | **Fax:** (850) 488-4876

Copyright 2011 – 2024 The Florida Channel. All Rights Reserved. | [Privacy Policy](https://thefloridachannel.org/privacy-policy/ "Privacy Policy")
